San Luis Potosí, México

🛘 (+52) 4441 70 55 48 | 🗷 arturguay@gmail.com | 🌴 arturocastillo.co | 🖸 arturocastillo95 | 🛅 arturo-castillo-a04877b1

"Life is a continuos excersise in creativity and problem solving."

Summary

I specialize in finding new and creative solutions to existing problems using a combination of my different skills in technology, marketing, design and business. I've been working for over 5 years with multiple organizations to resolve their technological needs and help improve their online presence.

Experience

Localito S.A.S. San Luis Potoí, México

CO-FOUNDER & SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Apr. 2020 - Currently

- Currently developing an MVP for my own SaaS business. The software is designed to help local business get their product catalog online in a
 matter of minutes.
- · Developing the web app based on Django, HTML, Javascript, CSS and several other technologies.
- · At the moment I'm working on deploying web app usig Heroku and Amazon RDS, focusing on high-availability, and auto-scaling.

Moran y CIA. San Luis Potosí, México

AUTOMATION & MARKETING CONSULTANT

Nov. 2019 - May. 2020

- · Implemented a new e-learning platform using custom software developed by myself and existing Wordpress solutions.
- · Built fully automated sales pipelines.
- · Developed internal software and scripts to automate tasks such as: billing, email marketing, sales follow-up, course completion certificates.

Freelance developer México

Website Developer Sep. 2015 - Currently

• Developed and designed multiple websites and landing pages for local businesses.

Jaguar Entertainment San Luis Potosí, México

CO-FOUNDER & CREATIVE DIRECTOR

May. 2017 - Nov 2019

- Created and produced multiple large scale events with thousands of attendants.
- Financial planning to ensure production profitability of every event.

Education

EBC (Escuela Bancaria y comercial)

San Luis Potosí, México

B.S. IN BUSINESS MANAGMENT

Feb. 2016 - May. 2020

• Participated in multiple startup incubation programs.

Skills_

Front-end HTML5, React, CSS, SASS, JQuery

Back-end Django, REST API

Programming Python, Javascript, Swift

DevOps AWS, Google cloud

Marketing Facebook Ads, Google ADS, Hubspot CRM, Mautic

Languages Spanish, English